<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mini_projet</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Titre_News1_sport">The Antique Nations Cup in football</string>
    <string name="Titre_News2_sport">The Six Nations Carousel, the 2024 Men\'s Euro Football</string>
    <string name="Titre_News3_sport">Paralympic sports</string>
    <string name="Titre_News4_sport">The Paris 2024 Paralympic Games</string>
    <string name="Titre_News5_sport">The Polymerized Games</string>
    <string name="Titre_News6_sport">Ronaldo, la sortie fracassante</string>
    <string name="Titre_News7_sport">Paris 2024, quelles chances de médailles chez les Français ?</string>
    <string name="Titre_News8_sport">Terrible annonce pour le FC Barcelone</string>

    <string name="Desc_News1_sport">Who will triumph in Senegal? The Antique Nations Cup (CAN) in Côte d\'Ivoire has unveiled its schedule. It will unfold in five cities and six stadiums, starting from January 13, 2024. The final winner will be crowned on February 11 after a month of intense competition. The groups for the 2024 Africa Cup of Nations are Group A: Côte d\'Ivoire, Guinea-Bissau, Equatorial Guinea, Nigeria. Group B: Mozambique, Cape Verde, Ghana, Egypt. Group C: Gambia, Guinea, Cameroon, Senegal. Group D: Angola, Mauritania, Burkina Faso, Algeria. Group E: Namibia, South Africa, Mali, Tunisia. Group F: Tanzania, Zambia, Democratic Republic of the Congo, Morocco.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News2_sport">How does EURO 2024 unfold? The final phase of the UEFA EURO 2024 is set to take place from June 14 to July 14, 2024. Germany qualifies for the final phase as the host country, meaning each nation will play a 14th EURO tournament. East and West Germany have featured in every EURO since 1972. West Germany won the 1972 and 1980 editions, while reunified Germany triumphed at EURO 96.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News3_sport">There are currently 28 Paralympic sports sanctioned by the IPCNBSP: 22 in summer and six in winter. The two most recent sports to achieve Paralympic status are badminton and taekwondo, both making their debut at the Tokyo 2020 Games. The newest winter sport is snowboarding, introduced for the first time at the 2014 Sochi Paralympic Games.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News4_sport">The Paris 2024 Paralympic Games will take place from August 28 to September 8, 2024, over twelve days of celebration during which the world will applaud the extraordinary performances of exceptional athletes. The Games are not just about sports but much more – a combination of cultural events, artistic programming, and diverse performances that create a unique experience. The Games are a popular and multicultural festival that reaches out to the entire world.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News5_sport">The venue for the 329 events of the Paris Olympic Games will be in the capital or the Île-de-France departments starting from July 24, 2024. France 3 Paris Île-de-France provides an overview of the schedule. From the capital to Seine-Saint-Denis, passing through Elancourt in Yvelines, the Île-de-France region will be the beating heart of the sports world from July 24 to August 11, 2024. For the Paris 2024 Olympic Games, competitions will start two days before the opening ceremony, which will take place on the Seine. Here is a complete schedule, department by department and day by day, of all the disciplines contested on French soil.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News6_sport">Cristiano Ronaldo a fini 2023 avec le sourire. Le Portugais a encore marqué avec Al-Nassr,lors de la victoire de son équipe contre Al-Taawon (1-4), et le voilà à 54 buts sur l’année civile.
 « Je suis heureux, a réagi le Portugais sur la télévision saoudienne au moment de faire le bilan de son année.
J’ai marqué beaucoup de buts. Je veux recommencer, je veux encore être le buteur mondial en 2024. «
Ronaldo se vante ainsi d’avoir fait mieux que les autres machines à marquer qui évoluent toujours en Europe.
CR7 a inscrit deux buts de plus que Harry Kane et Kylian Mbappé, et quatre de plus qu’Erling Haaland.
 Et il n’est pas peu fier de répondre ainsi à ceux qui pensaient qu’il était bon pour la retraite.
« 54. Je vous dirai quand j’en aurai terminé », a-t-il ainsi lancé via Instagram.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News7_sport">A partir du 26 juillet prochain, les Jeux Olympiques de Paris 2024 s’élanceront et la délégation française
 espère évidemment les achever avec le plus de médailles possibles. Les chances de breloques sont multiples
chez les hommes qui auront une certaine pression sur les épaules en tant qu’athlètes évoluant à domicile.
Léon Marchand (21 ans) a déjà prouvé que malgré son jeune âge, il pouvait s’en affranchir. Le nageur triple
 médaillé d’or aux Mondiaux de Fukuoka visera le summum sur le quatre nages, la brasse et le papillon.
Maxime Grousset (24 ans), champion du monde sur le 100m papillon et champion d’Europe sur le 100m nage
libre, sera aussi attendu. Florent Manaudou (33 ans) espère quant à lui jouer les premiers rôles sur sa distance
 fétiche du 50m nage libre.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News8_sport">Depuis qu’il a pris la succession du démissionnaire Josep Maria Bartomeu, au poste de président du FC Barcelone, Joan Laporta se démène pour tenter de redresser une situation financière catastrophique. Mais la tâche est rude et malgré de nombreux prêts contractés auprès des banques, il se pourrait bien que de dramatiques décisions doivent être prises dans les mois à venir. C’est en tout cas la teneur des propos de Joan Laporta, rapportés par Sport.\nSelon le média espagnol, le patron du Barça s’est fixé trois objectifs pour 2024.
D’abord celui de retrouver un Camp Nou flambant neuf et d’y rejouer le 29 novembre,
pour un premier match depuis le début des travaux de rénovation. Ensuite, de remporter de
 nouveaux titres avec l’équipe première. Et comme troisième vœux, celui de respecter le budget fixé
pour la saison. Et c’est là que tout se corse, car il s’agira pour lui et sa direction de faire entrer 859
millions d’euros dans les caisses, le tout avec un bénéfice de 11 millions d’euros.</string>

    <string name="Titre_News1_economie">Parliament confirms extension to all food products until the end of 2024</string>
    <string name="Titre_News2_economie">Maritime transport in the Red Sea: US announces coalition against Houthi attacks</string>
    <string name="Titre_News3_economie">Green hydrogen: "Japanese, Brazilians, Saudis, everyone questions the cost"</string>
    <string name="Titre_News4_economie">COP28: "Intelligent sequencing of institutional reforms, investment programs, and social reforms does not slow down climate action"</string>
    <string name="Titre_News5_economie">Russian oil deliveries to India hampered as Moscow refuses payment in rupees</string>
    <string name="Titre_News6_economie">It\'s time to admit the economy is thriving</string>
    <string name="Titre_News7_economie">China’s economy had a miserable year. 2024 might be even worse</string>
    <string name="Titre_News8_economie">How Putin is preparing Russia for a long war in Ukraine</string>

    <string name="Desc_News1_economie">Dishes of the day, sandwiches, salads, as well as flour, meat, pasta, or bread… Meal vouchers will remain valid until the end of 2024 for any type of food purchase. Parliament hastily adopted, on Monday, December 18, by a final vote in the Senate, the extension of the exemption put in place in 2022. The text, presented by the government as a measure to fight persistently high inflation, was adopted by 322 votes against 2 by the senators in the evening.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News2_economie">The US Secretary of Defense announced on Monday, December 18, the formation of a coalition of ten countries in the Red Sea to address repeated attacks by the Houthis on ships they consider "linked to Israel." In addition to the United States, Lloyd Austin indicated in a statement that France, the United Kingdom, Bahrain, Canada, Italy, the Netherlands, Norway, Spain, and the Seychelles would participate in this coalition.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News3_economie">Honestly, there are few projects making concrete progress. In 2021, many consulting firms and institutions sold low-carbon hydrogen as a miracle solution, but it\'s more complicated than it seems. Whether talking to the Japanese, Brazilians, or Saudis, everyone asks the same question: about demand due to the high cost of this energy source.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News4_economie">Given the increasing concentration of greenhouse gases in the atmosphere, it\'s natural to consider the outcome of the twenty-eight UN climate conferences as insufficient. However, we must not forget the progress made, including the commitments of 101 countries aiming for net zero emissions in a few decades. Analyses conducted by the World Bank in over forty countries show that, thanks to recent technological advances, it\'s now possible to achieve our climate goals without compromising economic development or poverty reduction.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News5_economie">India\'s rush for Russian oil is complicated. As the tanker NS Century, sanctioned by Washington, has been waiting off the Indian coast since late November for New Delhi\'s green light to dock, payment issues hinder deliveries. According to Reuters and Bloomberg, citing anonymous sources, Russia refuses to be paid in rupees, while India is reluctant to settle purchases in yuan, the currency of its Chinese rival.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News6_economie">  By contrast, Stancil noticed the 2021 economy was rebounding back from a brief but painful pandemic-induced recession: Wages were growing, people still had a savings cushion, and spending was up.
And the data has only gotten better. The unemployment rate has now been under 4% for 22 months straight, per BLS, the longest such stretch in over 50 years. The country added more jobs than expected in November. Layoff rates are still hovering near historic lows.
The much-discussed and feared recession hasn\'t arrived. Yes, inflation is up, but people have jobs and are able to keep spending. Americans did just that this holiday season, with retail sales up 3.1% during the holiday stretch from November 1 to December 24, according to data from MasterCard SpendingPulse.
Blue-collar workers, meanwhile, have made big economic strides, but those stories have been crowded out by headlines about layoffs at major tech and media companies. Wage increases have largely kept up with inflation but have surpassed it for lower-income workers. Real wages were up 0.8% year-over-year in November, which was most pronounced among lower-income Americans.
</string>
    <string name="Desc_News7_economie">The Chinese economy, which is plagued by a litany of challenges, didn’t get to this position overnight.
Scissors said the previous administration of President Hu Jintao had flooded the economy with liquidity in 2009 during the depths of the global financial crisis to boost growth. Xi’s government was reluctant to rein in the borrowing after coming to power in 2012, which caused structural problems to build up.
Logan Wright, director of China markets research at Rhodium Group, agreed, saying: “The slowdown in China’s economy is structural, caused by the end of an unprecedented expansion in credit and investment over the past decade.”
The country’s financial system simply won’t be able to generate the same levels of credit growth that it has in previous years, he said, therefore Beijing will have far less control over the direction of its economy than it has in the past.
What made things worse was Beijing’s stubborn embrace of a zero-Covid policy of stringent lockdowns and its sweeping crackdown on private enterprise, which deeply hurt confidence and battered the most vibrant part of the economy.
</string>
    <string name="Desc_News8_economie" formatted="false">Russian despot Vladimir Putin has pushed his nation onto a permanent war footing, after signing a three-year draft budget that has committed to spending more than 6% of Russia\'s GDP on war spending.
A third of government spending in 2024 will be on the military alone, according to the draft budget.
While some of this is set to be paid for by increased oil revenues, spending in other public sectors, including housing, education and healthcare, are set to be slashed.
Education is expected to decline from 4.8por of total government spending in 2023 to 4.2por in 2024, while healthcare spending is expected to fall from 5.2% in 2023 to 4.4% in 2024.
Russia has also diverted funds for a $400bn (£314bn) national projects programme that aimed to improve living standards in Russia, by spending money on infrastructure and diversifying the economy away from natural resources.
</string>
    <string name="Titre_News1_sante">Over 6,700 full hospitalization beds closed in France in 2022</string>
    <string name="Titre_News2_sante">Never has the publication of any law or decree since 1979 worried professionals like us</string>
    <string name="Titre_News3_sante">"IVF is risky medicine in the absence of preimplantation diagnosis"</string>
    <string name="Titre_News4_sante">Health insurance, salary, and mandatory annual negotiations</string>
    <string name="Titre_News5_sante">Violence against healthcare workers: a communication campaign to "change behaviors"</string>
    <string name="Titre_News6_sante">WHO Urges the World to Better Prepare for Future Pandemics</string>
    <string name="Titre_News7_sante">Global Health: Crucial Challenges for the Next 10 Years</string>
    <string name="Titre_News8_sante">Addiction Specialists Fear E-cigarettes Will Bear the Brunt of Anti-Tobacco Plan</string>
    <string name="Desc_News1_sante" formatted="false">The downward trend continues for twenty years: as of December 31, 2022, the 2,976 public and private hospitals had exactly 374,290 full hospitalization beds, 6,713 fewer than the previous year, according to the statistical department of the social ministries (Drees) report published on Wednesday, December 20. Healthcare facilities, during the same period, created 2,591 day hospitalization places, without overnight stays, for a total of 85,015 places. Unlike a bed, a day place can usually accommodate several daily patients.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News2_sante" formatted="false"> The National Association of Abortion and Contraception Centers (Ancic), a professional association for abortion established in 1979, has been vigilant since the final vote on the Veil law to defend women\'s rights to control their bodies and those of abortion professionals in their practice. After welcoming the March 2022 passage of the Gaillot law aimed at strengthening abortion rights, and eagerly awaiting the release of the implementing decree that extends the competence of instrumental abortion procedures to midwives in healthcare facilities, we are now dismayed by Article D.2212–8–1 of this decree.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News3_sante" formatted="false">However, in the case of IVF, it\'s now possible to analyze very young embryos (three to six days) using preimplantation genetic diagnosis, also known as PGD-A. This examination verifies that embryos are not carriers of chromosomal or metabolic abnormalities before their implantation in the woman\'s uterus. These anomalies are common, present in 40% to 90% of embryos, depending on the age of the patients. When this happens, these embryos, called "aneuploid," will not result in the birth of a healthy child. Women undergoing IVF are often older, increasing these anomalies and the risks of conception failure.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News4_sante">Office notebook. In the time of mandatory annual negotiations (MAN) on remuneration, HR perspectives tend to shift. When HR departments lack sufficient budgetary allocations for significant salary increases, either because the company is in trouble or the group\'s strategy sets other priorities, or for any other reason, the first option explored is "other employee benefits," such as health insurance.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News5_sante">The slogan should not leave anyone indifferent: "You have to be sick to attack a healthcare professional," reads three posters featuring a nurse, a doctor, and a pharmacist, each a victim of violence. Starting Tuesday, December 19, and for a month, it will be disseminated on social networks and displayed in healthcare facilities – hospitals, pharmacies, medical offices. This communication campaign aims to "change the behavior of violent patients" and "encourage victim professionals to file complaints," according to the Ministry of Health.</string>
    <string name="Desc_News6_sante">After finally putting an end to three years of "crisis, suffering, and losses" related to Covid in 2023, the world must properly prepare for future pandemics, said the head of the WHO on Tuesday. The Director-General of the World Health Organization, Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus, emphasized that this year had marked a turning point in the fight against major health issues, but there had also been “immense suffering that could have been avoided.”
In his year-end message, Tedros called for an intensification of humanitarian efforts for the Gaza Strip and urged countries to reach an “unprecedented” agreement to fill gaps in preparation for the next pandemic. “The year 2024 offers a unique opportunity to bridge these gaps,” he said, reminding that countries are negotiating the world’s first global agreement on pandemic threats.</string>

    <string name="Desc_News7_sante">We must realize that health is an investment in the future. Countries invest heavily to protect their population from terrorist attacks but not from virus attacks, which can be much more deadly and economically and socially harmful. A pandemic could bring the economy and nations to their knees. Therefore, health security cannot be solely the responsibility of health ministries.
As a new year and a new decade begins, the WHO publishes a list of crucial health challenges worldwide. This list, established with the participation of experts from around the world, arises from deep concern. Indeed, leaders are not investing enough in health priorities and essential health systems, thereby endangering lives, livelihoods, and economies. None of these issues is easy to resolve, but the solutions are within our reach. Ultimately, public health is a political choice.</string>

    <string name="Desc_News8_sante">The Health Minister presented a new anti-tobacco plan this Tuesday. In addition to a price increase for the pack until 2026, smokers will no longer be able to smoke in certain public places. But the government also intends to tackle electronic cigarettes. A mistake for some addiction specialists.
12 euros in 2025, 13 euros in 2026… The price of a pack of cigarettes will continue to rise in France as part of a new anti-tobacco plan presented this Tuesday by the Health Minister, Aurélien Rousseau. Already in effect in 73 departments, the ban on smoking in certain public places, such as forests, beaches, or around schools, will also be extended nationwide.
But electronic cigarettes are also in the crosshairs of the state. With this new plan, products for electronic cigarettes will now have plain packaging, without logos or brands like traditional cigarettes. The Ministry of Health also wants to limit the available flavors for purchase.</string>
</resources>